GET IN TOUCH WITH ME

- Toronto ON M6H2H6
- <u>+1 (647) 631 48 48</u>
- <u>barmashev48@gmail.com</u>
- <u>www.ermekcodes.com</u>
- in @ermek-barmashev
- @barmashev48

SKILLS

- HTML, CSS, SCSS
- JavaScript, React, Redux, JQuery
- Git/GitHub
- RESTful APIs, Firebase
- Responsive Design, Web Accessibility

ERMEK BARMASHEV

WEB DEVELOPER

PERSONAL PROFILE

I am a web developer with experience in customer service and sales/marketing who is committed to making the web more accessible and user-friendly. I love writing clean code and learning new technologies as well as collaborating with team members on the projects.

EDUCATIONAL HISTORY

Juno College of Technology

Web Development Bootcamp | 2021

Al-Farabi National University

BA International Law | 2012 - 2016

FEATURED PROJECTS

Likely Match (VIEW LIVE)

React | CSS | Firebase

This app generates a playlist of similar songs based on a user's input

Blackjack (VIEW LIVE)

HTML | CSS | JQuery

A game of Blackjack that deals cards to the player and a dealer, counts the cards and displays the winner

SELECTED WORK EXPERIENCE

Lead Cashier

Summerhill Market | Feb 2020 - Oct 2020

- Managed a group of cashiers during the first wave of the COVID pandemic ensuring the safety of the customers and the staff
- Trained new cashiers
- Answering customer inquiries in an efficient, friendly manner

Sales Intern (Market Strategy & Planning)

Procter & Gamble | Feb 2019 - Jun 2019

- Managed Oral Care category in Kazakhstan
- Successfully worked with the marketing and distribution team to launch a new line of oral care products for the Central Asian Market
- Created and presented a market overview to the Regional Director to assist in the onboarding process